<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Academics on Monique&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://mlswebsite.github.io/categories/academics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Academics on Monique&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>zh-cn</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://mlswebsite.github.io/categories/academics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Fountianhead- Q3</title>
      <link>https://mlswebsite.github.io/post/essay-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mlswebsite.github.io/post/essay-3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Dominique Francon loves Roark, yet she struggles to destroy his career. Why? What does she come to understand over the course of the novel that ultimately convinces her to change her mind? How does this conflict of hers relate to the novel’s theme and meaning? In your answer, refer to both The Fountainhead and “Introduction to the Twenty-fifth Anniversary Edition” of The Fountainhead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Dominique is a conflicted character that pursues her idealism yet is confined to the world by her pessimism. She loves Roark, because he embodies everything she values: greatness, purity, desire, and freedom from social constraints. Dominique admires his greatness, although it is for the same reason that she attempts to destroy his career. She believes that greatness is doomed to fail, to be corrupted by the mediocre, so that’s why she destroys his career.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Fountianhead- Q2</title>
      <link>https://mlswebsite.github.io/post/essay-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mlswebsite.github.io/post/essay-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Introduction to the Twenty-fifth Anniversary Edition Many people have asked me how I feel about the fact that The Fountainhead has been in print for twenty-five years. I cannot say that I feel anything in particular, except a kind of quiet satisfaction. In this respect, my attitude toward my writing is best expressed by a statement of Victor Hugo: &amp;ldquo;If a writer wrote merely for his time, I would have to break my pen and throw it away.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Fountianhead- Q1</title>
      <link>https://mlswebsite.github.io/post/essay-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mlswebsite.github.io/post/essay-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“He rose, beamed and held Dominique&amp;rsquo;s hand. “Thought I&amp;rsquo;d drop in on my way home,” he said. “I&amp;rsquo;ve got something to tell you. How did it go, kid?”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“As I expected it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;She tore her hat off and threw it down on the first chair in sight. Her hair slanted in a flat curve across her forehead and fell in a straight line to her shoulders; it looked smooth and tight, like a bathing cap of pale, polished metal. She walked to the window and stood looking out over the city. She asked without turning: “What did you want to tell me?”&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>macroeconomics ASAD</title>
      <link>https://mlswebsite.github.io/post/macroeconomics-asad/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mlswebsite.github.io/post/macroeconomics-asad/</guid>
      <description>&lt;video width=&#34;100%&#34; controls loop&gt;&#xA;  &lt;source src=&#34;macroeconomics ASAD.mp4&#34; type=&#34;video/mp4&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/video&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IMMC International 2024: Assessing Family Pet Ownership Based on Multi-Model Correlation Analysis</title>
      <link>https://mlswebsite.github.io/post/immc24397795/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mlswebsite.github.io/post/immc24397795/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;1-abstract&#34;&gt;1. Abstract&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;During the long river of human history, humans and pets are inseparable. Pets are&#xA;treasured due to the joy they’ve brought owners and the companionship it brings, cre-&#xA;ating loving memories. The pet market has risen in the few years, especially during the&#xA;COVID, when the number of pet owners surged. At the same time, however, more and&#xA;more pets are getting abandoned, ending up stray and overcrowding the shelters, creat-&#xA;ing a big burden. People have long been confused of who’s suitable for raising pets, and&#xA;concerns have been increasing everywhere. To handle this situation, this article will ex-&#xA;plore a decision evaluating model that help determine what households are suitable for&#xA;owning a pet and forecasts future pet ownership.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IMMC First round: 国际赛（中华区）建模大赛（B 题）</title>
      <link>https://mlswebsite.github.io/post/immc24199225/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mlswebsite.github.io/post/immc24199225/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;摘要&#34;&gt;摘要&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;自古至今，屋顶在人们的生活中不可缺，它不仅起到遮风、挡雨、防晒、保温、隔热的作用，同时还代表着家庭和睦、民生安全，更在历史中象征着权力地位。屋顶所处地区的气候特征影响屋顶屋顶结构，人们的品味、历史的进程，也在潜移默化地作用于屋顶结构样式的演进。不同地区的屋顶样式、曲度、坡度各不相同，每一种屋顶都有其独特的优势，亦存在缺陷。长久以来人们试图找到最适合某一地区的最优屋顶配置，但由于环境、经济、人文的多种因素，此问题很难完美解答。因此，本文根据题目中的三个问题，试图找到不同地区屋顶的最佳配置。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
