<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Speech Drafts on Monique&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://mlswebsite.github.io/tags/speech-drafts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Speech Drafts on Monique&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>zh-cn</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://mlswebsite.github.io/tags/speech-drafts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Catching Butterflies</title>
      <link>https://mlswebsite.github.io/post/catching-butterflies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mlswebsite.github.io/post/catching-butterflies/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Butterflies. What is the first thing that comes to mind when you hear it? It could be the butterfly fluttering in the meadow. But for me, it is the butterflies flying in my stomach. So now you might understand why this x-ray picture with butterflies is doing here. This, quite literally, is just having butterflies in your stomach. So why is it here?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let me just begin with telling you what having ‘butterflies in your stomach’ means. This describes the nervous energy in your belly before or during situations where you might feel anxious or excited. I hate this feeling, but you see me standing here, which means I have caught some of them (grabs some of it).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beauty of Books</title>
      <link>https://mlswebsite.github.io/post/beauty-of-books/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mlswebsite.github.io/post/beauty-of-books/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I’ve heard a lot of unique topics, so I’m going to start with something common &amp;ndash; books. No matter text books we use for class, books we read outside of school for research, novels for relaxing… Books are woven into our lives.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Do you remember the first time you read a book? I couldn’t. But that feeling was something I’d always remember. It felt as if we had an immediate bond, and I couldn’t take my eyes off the intricate and fancy pictures. From the soft, fabricated touch of my first book to the scratchy paper and smooth cover of my recent books, I loved reading. Books have been my companions on adventures through time and space, making it a friend worthy of love and time.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Line of passion</title>
      <link>https://mlswebsite.github.io/post/line-of-passion-24.5.20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mlswebsite.github.io/post/line-of-passion-24.5.20/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today I’m going to start with something common in our lives—books. I don’t know if you could remember properly the first time when you started reading a book. I couldn’t. But that feeling was something I’d always remember. It felt as if we had an immediate bond, and I couldn’t take my eyes off the intricate and fancy pictures. From the soft, fabricated touch of my first book to the scratchy paper and smooth cover of my recent books, I loved reading. I don’t understand passion or love that clearly, but books have been my companions on adventures through time and space, making it a friend worthy of love and time.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speech</title>
      <link>https://mlswebsite.github.io/post/%E6%BC%94%E8%AE%B2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mlswebsite.github.io/post/%E6%BC%94%E8%AE%B2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;WechatIMG24.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;2024.5&#34;&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;WechatIMG11.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;2024.9&#34;&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;WechatIMG12.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;2025.9&#34;&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
