<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Behavioral Economics on Monique&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://mlswebsite.github.io/tags/behavioral-economics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Behavioral Economics on Monique&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>zh-cn</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://mlswebsite.github.io/tags/behavioral-economics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The relationship between Loss Aversion Preferences and Academic Performance</title>
      <link>https://mlswebsite.github.io/post/loss-aversion--academic-performance/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mlswebsite.github.io/post/loss-aversion--academic-performance/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;WORK IN PROGRESS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attitude Towards Loss Aversion: The Differences Across Age and Gender in China</title>
      <link>https://mlswebsite.github.io/post/attitude-towards-loss-aversion/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mlswebsite.github.io/post/attitude-towards-loss-aversion/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;abstract&#34;&gt;Abstract&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This study investigates the extent to which loss aversion varies across age and gender&#xA;in China. Employing an online, survey-based method, this study uses econometric&#xA;approaches (regression models and the utility function in stata) and examines Chinese people&#xA;of all ages and genders to assess loss aversion through mixed lottery questions. The findings&#xA;are inconsistent with the hypothesis, revealing that gender and age aren’t significantly related&#xA;to loss aversion. There seemed to be no significant differences between women and men,&#xA;although men are a bit more loss-averse than women. Older people are found to be more loss-&#xA;averse than younger people. These results contribute to the understanding of loss aversion in&#xA;a cultural context and provide new insights into gender differences. Questions and research&#xA;topics are proposed for further understanding and further research.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
