<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Film Review on Monique&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://mlswebsite.github.io/tags/film-review/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Film Review on Monique&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>zh-cn</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://mlswebsite.github.io/tags/film-review/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Pearl (Movie) Analysis</title>
      <link>https://mlswebsite.github.io/post/pearl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mlswebsite.github.io/post/pearl/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;She is highly sympathetic yet also disturbingly unhinged. She’s trapped in a suffocating environment after the first world war, burdened with caring for her paralyzed father and living under her mother’s strict authority. Yet she dreams to be a star- a dancer that will one day famous, like such in the Hollywood movies.&#xA;At the beginning of the film, Pearl admires herself in the mirror. She believes that the image in the mirror (her ideal self) is the sweet, glamorous movie star (yet the role is acutally shaped by the American Dream). It kinda feels like ‘the mirror stage’ Lacan mentioned. During this stage, infants recognize themselves in the mirror. The reflected self appears whole and unified, but the actual self is fragmented and uncoordinated. From this gap, the infant constructs an ‘ideal ego,’ a seemingly complete and coherent self-image. Pearl believes that herself in the mirror is a star, yet it is found on misrecognition, as Pearl can never become the cinematic ideal she chases.  She refuses to believe it, yet her mother’s words and her failed audition keeps reminding her that she never will become the Hollywood star she imagines herself to be.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>致最真实的女主：写在看完《好想做一次》之后 (Never Have I Ever)</title>
      <link>https://mlswebsite.github.io/post/never-have-i-ever/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mlswebsite.github.io/post/never-have-i-ever/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;我是一个看完影片就喜欢刷评论的人 。在看完《好想做一次》全四季后，我兴高采烈的去不同网站上翻评论和看点评去了。令我诧异的是，Devi（主角）这个角色的行为/性格包含争议：有些人很喜欢她，又有些人很讨厌她。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ender’s Game movie review</title>
      <link>https://mlswebsite.github.io/post/enders-game-movie-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mlswebsite.github.io/post/enders-game-movie-review/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;In the moment when I truly understand my enemy, understand him well enough to defeat him, then in that very moment I also love him. I think it&amp;rsquo;s impossible to really understand somebody, what they want, what they believe, and not love them the way they love themselves.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While I was scrolling through movies, I came across Ender’s game. I haven’t read the book before, so my reviews are only on the movie and some comments and reviews others had on the book. The movie was about people training an army used to fight the Formics (sort of like ants), and Ender was the main character who’s destined to lead the team into winning the war. Personally, I believe that it was a good movie, although there were parts that I was confused with or could be better.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
