<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Writings on Monique&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://mlswebsite.github.io/tags/writings/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Writings on Monique&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>zh-cn</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://mlswebsite.github.io/tags/writings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Dream</title>
      <link>https://mlswebsite.github.io/post/dreams/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mlswebsite.github.io/post/dreams/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;WORK IN PROGRESS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Journal One</title>
      <link>https://mlswebsite.github.io/post/grief/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mlswebsite.github.io/post/grief/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;WORK IN PROGRESS&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;October 1st&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It’s been five months since she died. People still look at me as if I’m some question they’re too polite to ask. I sit quiet during the funeral, my black shirt swaying with the wind. The wind blows; it howls, seemingly mourning for my encounter. Besides the wind, everything else was still. Guests shuffled around me, phrases of ‘everything happens for a reason’, ‘it’s a miracle you were spared’ ‘you have to move on’ passed into my ear. They were like droplets of rain, fragile, empty, and disappeared quickly. One ear in, out the other.&#xA;I guess everyone wanted me to believe that her death was a comma in some divine sentence, which I thought it wasn’t. It felt like a typo one made and didn’t care to change.&#xA;I met our parents. I see my mother dabbing her tears onto her handkerchief as if she could press them away. I saw my father lowering his head. I guess he didn’t want guests to see him crying. I sat beside them during the funeral. No words were exchanged.&#xA;I guess they rather wished it was me who died.&#xA;I did too.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Final Project</title>
      <link>https://mlswebsite.github.io/post/final-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mlswebsite.github.io/post/final-project/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Screams.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Blood curling screams. Blood that runs like a river. Flesh molded together. Tangled and scattered limbs. Achilles stood in front of him. The head of the spear flew close to him. Everything seemed to happen in slow motion. Then it was pain.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Crucifying pain.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The bronze dagger seemed to pierce through frozen time as it inched towards Hector’s abdominal. It burst right through his sides, and heat seemed to spread towards his whole body. He looked down and thought he’d seen red run up towards him. His eyes slowly closed as the ground rushed to greet him. Is this how it’s supposed to end? The hero, defender of Troy, lay slack on the grounds, as he watched the Greek trample down his home.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
