<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ayn Rand Competition on Monique&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://mlswebsite.github.io/tags/ayn-rand-competition/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ayn Rand Competition on Monique&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>zh-cn</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://mlswebsite.github.io/tags/ayn-rand-competition/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Fountianhead- Q3</title>
      <link>https://mlswebsite.github.io/post/essay-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mlswebsite.github.io/post/essay-3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Dominique Francon loves Roark, yet she struggles to destroy his career. Why? What does she come to understand over the course of the novel that ultimately convinces her to change her mind? How does this conflict of hers relate to the novel’s theme and meaning? In your answer, refer to both The Fountainhead and “Introduction to the Twenty-fifth Anniversary Edition” of The Fountainhead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Dominique is a conflicted character that pursues her idealism yet is confined to the world by her pessimism. She loves Roark, because he embodies everything she values: greatness, purity, desire, and freedom from social constraints. Dominique admires his greatness, although it is for the same reason that she attempts to destroy his career. She believes that greatness is doomed to fail, to be corrupted by the mediocre, so that’s why she destroys his career.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Fountianhead- Q2</title>
      <link>https://mlswebsite.github.io/post/essay-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mlswebsite.github.io/post/essay-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Introduction to the Twenty-fifth Anniversary Edition Many people have asked me how I feel about the fact that The Fountainhead has been in print for twenty-five years. I cannot say that I feel anything in particular, except a kind of quiet satisfaction. In this respect, my attitude toward my writing is best expressed by a statement of Victor Hugo: &amp;ldquo;If a writer wrote merely for his time, I would have to break my pen and throw it away.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Fountianhead- Q1</title>
      <link>https://mlswebsite.github.io/post/essay-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mlswebsite.github.io/post/essay-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“He rose, beamed and held Dominique&amp;rsquo;s hand. “Thought I&amp;rsquo;d drop in on my way home,” he said. “I&amp;rsquo;ve got something to tell you. How did it go, kid?”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“As I expected it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;She tore her hat off and threw it down on the first chair in sight. Her hair slanted in a flat curve across her forehead and fell in a straight line to her shoulders; it looked smooth and tight, like a bathing cap of pale, polished metal. She walked to the window and stood looking out over the city. She asked without turning: “What did you want to tell me?”&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
