<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>AP on Monique&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://mlswebsite.github.io/tags/ap/</link>
    <description>Recent content in AP on Monique&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>zh-cn</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://mlswebsite.github.io/tags/ap/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hubristic syndrome Assessing its literary applications through The Great Gatsby and Agamemnon</title>
      <link>https://mlswebsite.github.io/post/hubristic-syndrome/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mlswebsite.github.io/post/hubristic-syndrome/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;From the ancient tragedies of Greece to the modern-day downfalls of business tycoons and political leaders, the concept of hubris has served as a cautionary tale about the perils of unchecked power. The theme hubris was already apparent in Greek tragedies, where it mostly meant disrespecting the gods by not crediting ones’ success or fortune to the gods (Marquez, 2015), often leading to nemesis (divine retribution) and ate (ruin). The meaning of hubris has then evolved into excessive arrogance and over-confidence that leads to self-destruction (Marquez, 2015).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self Determination Theory</title>
      <link>https://mlswebsite.github.io/post/self-determination-theory/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mlswebsite.github.io/post/self-determination-theory/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In a psychological view, self-determination means the result or process of acting under one’s own choice, ‘particularly to behaviours that improves one’s circumstance’ (APA dictionary of psychology, 2018; Merriam-Webster, n.d.). Self-determination is useful in overcoming fears, giving humans the courage to achieve more, as did Jerry when going through the tunnel (Lessing, 1957), bringing him growth and maturity. For adolescents, or even young children like Jerry, self-determination could help them make vocational decisions, informed choices, and increase independence (Field, Hoffman, Posch 1997). Increased motivation and satisfaction of three fundamental needs also increases self- determination, helping ones to persevere through challenges. Elouise Cobell presents such characteristic when going against the U.S. government, fighting for the rights of the Blackfoot tribe, bringing justice eventually (Janko, 2013).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Companion Animal Cloning from a Scientific Viewpoint</title>
      <link>https://mlswebsite.github.io/post/companion-animal-cloning-from-a-scientific-viewpoint/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mlswebsite.github.io/post/companion-animal-cloning-from-a-scientific-viewpoint/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;From Dolly the Sheep to Snuppy the Dog, pet cloning is gaining more attention, and the number of people who are considering using this technique to resurrect their pet is climbing. Since commencing operations in 2015, Viagen, a company specializing in pet cloning, has reported an increase in the number of cloning procedures performed. The company has disclosed completing hundreds of procedures to date (Dimitropoulos, 2022). But is this the right thing to do?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
