<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Psychology on Monique&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://mlswebsite.github.io/tags/psychology/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Psychology on Monique&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>zh-cn</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://mlswebsite.github.io/tags/psychology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>《瞬息全宇宙》中母女关系的变化——从结构主义到辩证法</title>
      <link>https://mlswebsite.github.io/post/%E7%9E%AC%E6%81%AF%E5%85%A8%E5%AE%87%E5%AE%99/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mlswebsite.github.io/post/%E7%9E%AC%E6%81%AF%E5%85%A8%E5%AE%87%E5%AE%99/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;摘要&#34;&gt;摘要&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This paper analyzes the evolving relationship between Evelyn and her daughter Joy in Everything Everywhere All at Once. We seek to answer the following question: Why does the relationship between Evelyn and her daughter undergo such a dramatic transformation?  The study analyzes such question through the theoretical lenses of structuralism and Hegelian dialectics, ultimately concluding that the root of the mother-daughter conflict lies in the failure of the Symbolic Order to fully symbolize the Real. Specifically, when facing the collapse of the symbolic order, Evelyn&amp;rsquo;s initial coping strategy - relying on &amp;lsquo;fantasy&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;adding signifiers that slips along the signifying chain&amp;rsquo; to suppress surplus - inevitably produces more surplus, as symbolization always generates new remnants. The excessive use of symbolization leads to the &amp;ldquo;death&amp;rdquo; of the subject. Evelyn’s resolution comes not through violently repressing surplus (her daughter’s loss of control), but through facing the surplus, and turning towards containment and symbiosis.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
